Thus, it is your profit that will continue to ride if it continues up.
Tip # 3
That you can sell half of your investment-
-If you've gone with SEK 10,000, yes, sell half.
Then you don't sell everything, so if it continues up-
-So you are still on the train, but you reduce your possible profit.
Then you have secured some money.
Tip number 4, it's not to sell everything at once.
If you have a share that has gone pretty well, as in my case where Sinch is worth SEK 200,000.
It's not that smart if I sell everything at once, but I can go out with a little at a time.
Kind of like I said in the previous tip, maybe sell half or distribute it into maybe four sales.
-But if it is so that it continues up, you have sold a little more expensive and get more profit.
Tip number 5, do not sell the shares.
You may be convinced that the company will go well or you may be wrong.
Why should you sell?
Really wondering if it's right to sell, because in most cases-
-So it is just short -term noise, that something is happening like viruses in society or whatever.
Which makes you doubt on your investment.
But it is true that quite often you are actually wrong and maybe should remain.
Alright, I'll tell you why I'm not going to sell my shares in Sinch.
From the beginning, it was so that I heard about the company Sinch first in the pod Market Makers.
Then I started doing some research, I started to look at this presentations from Sinch's CEO.